- 你们是谁 - 你们又是谁
- Who the hell are you? - Who the hell are you?
他失血太多 我们必须回去
He's bleeding out. We gotta go back.
过来 用力按住膝盖
Come around here. Put pressure on the knee.
用力 用力按
Hard, hard! Push, push.
从后面出来
Come on, outta there.
慢慢走
Slow and steady.
他怎么了
What happened to him?
- 他被咬了 - 被咬
- He got bit. - Bit?
别激动
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Easy now.
没有动武的必要
Nobody needs get hurt.
- 你使劲按住 - 好
- I need you to hold this. - Okay.
- 用最大力 - 是
- As hard as you can. - Yes.
你们有医疗品吗
You have medical supplies?
谁允许你过去了
Whoa, where do you think you're going?
你们到底是谁
Who the hell are you people, anyway?
你们可不像救援队
Don't look like no rescue team.
别妄想等到救援队了
If a rescue team is what you're waiting for, don't.
快 得走了
Come on, we gotta go.
过来 帮把手
Now! Come on! I need a hand here.
一二三 走
One, two, three, go!
- 老天 - T仔 开门
- Holy Jesus! - T, the door.
- 你疯了吗 不能开 - 别妨碍我们
- Are you crazy? Don't open that! - We got this.
达里尔 达里尔
Daryl. Daryl!
我们走
Let's go.
这边
This way.
《行尸走肉》
这边走
This way, this way.
不不 快后退
No, no, no. Back, back!
达里尔
Daryl.
跟上 快走
Come on! Go, go, go.
小心 注意点
Watch out, watch out.
都停下
Stop, stop.
跟着他们的光走
Follow the flashlight.
快走
Come on, let's go.
快走 走
Let's go. Go, go, go.
稳住
Easy, easy.
- 他失血太多了 - 快开门
- He's losing too much blood. - Open the door!
赫谢尔出事了
It's Hershel!
卡尔 快
Carl! Come on.
- 天啊 - 爸爸
- Oh, my God. - Daddy!
快到里面去
Go, go, go, go, go. In there.
这边
This way.
抬到床上
Get him on the bed.
他被咬了
He got bit.
- 老天 他会变成行尸 - 你们把腿砍了
- Oh, my God, he's gonna turn. - Did you cut it off?
- 是的 - 也许还来得及
- Yeah. - Maybe you got it in time.
- 准备 - 好
- Ready? - Okay.
一 二 三
One, two, three.
天
Oh, God.
我需要绷带
Oh, I need bandages.
- 医疗品都用完了 - 那就找点别的
- We used everything we had. - Well, get more. Anything.
卡尔 去把我床边的毛巾拿来
Carl, go get the towels from the back, right next to my bed.
- 他会变行尸吗 - 他会没事的
- Is he gonna turn? - He's gonna be okay.
你能稳住他的伤情吗
You think you can stabilize him?
得把他的腿抬高
I need to keep his leg elevated.
拿些枕头来
Get some pillows!
床单已经被血浸透了
He's already bled through the sheets.
可以用火烧伤口止血 我来点火
We can burn the wound to clot the blood. I can start a fire.
- 求你不要 - 不行 用火烧他挺不住的
- No, please don't do this. - No, the shock could kill him.
而且没法止住动脉出血
It's not gonna stop the artery from bleeding.
我们只能尽力止血让它自然愈合
We need to just keep it dressed and let it heal on its own.
别再靠近
That's far enough.
C单元区
Cell block C.
我住在4号牢房 美国佬
Cell 4… that's mine, gringo.
让我进去
Let me in.
你们哥几个今天运气不错
Today's your lucky days, fellas.
乔治亚州赦免了你们 你们可以走了
You've been pardoned by the state of Georgia. You are free to go.
里面情况怎样
What you got going on in there?
与你无关
It ain't none of your concern.
这可不是你说了算
Don't be telling me what's my concern.
冷静 伙计 那家伙腿都毁了
Chill, man. Dude's leg is messed up.
再说咱都自由了 还留这干什么
Besides, we're free now. Why are we still in here?
他说得对
The man's got a point.
我也想去找我老婆
Yeah, and I gotta check on my old lady.
普通市民突然之间
Oops, civilians break into a prison,
闯入监狱
and you got no business being in…
我想这说明已经没其他地方可去了吧
got me thinking there ain't no place for us to go.
- 你可以出去看看 - 我们正要去呢
- Why don't you go find out? - Maybe we'll just be going now.
- 我们不走 - 也不能进来
- Hey, we ain't leaving. - You ain't coming in either.
我的地盘我做主
It's my house, my rules.
我爱去哪儿去哪儿
I go where I damn will please.
- 那是谁 - 幸存的犯人
- What was that? - Prisoners, survivors.
- 什么 - 没事 大家别动
- What? - It's all right. Everybody stay put.
守在他身边
Do not leave his side.
如果他死了 你要准备好善后
If he dies, you need to be there for that.
能做到吗
You think you can do this?
- 玛姬也会在那 - 我可以
- Maggie will be there. - I got it.
- 要不让我T仔来… - 我可以
- I can bring T in here… - I got it.
很好
Good.
这里不欢迎你们
There ain't nothing for you here.
你们怎么不回之前那坑里蹲着
Why don't you go back to your own sandbox?
都放松 没必要这样
Everyone relax. There's no need for this.
你们有多少人
How many of you are in there?
比你想象的多
Too many for you to handle.
你们是不是抢了银行
Have you rob a bank or something?
为什么不带他去正规医院
Why don't you take him to a hospital?
你们在食堂困了多久
How long have you been locked in that cafeteria?
十个月了吧
Going on like 10 months.
监狱暴动了
A riot broke out.
从没见过那样的暴动
Never seen anything like it.
阿提卡暴动 1971年震惊全美的监狱暴动
听说过人变成食人魔
Ever heard about dudes going cannibal,
死而复生吗
dying, coming back to life?
太疯狂了
Crazy.
一个狱警为了保护我们 把我们锁在食堂
One guard looked out for us, locked us up in the cafeteria.
让我们别动
Told us to sit tight,
给了我这把枪 说他马上回来
throw me this piece and he'd be right back.
但已经过了292天
Yeah, and that was 292 days ago.
- 据我计算是294… - 闭嘴
- 94 accdiding to my calcula… - Shut up!
我们本以为军队或国民警卫队
We were thinking that the Army or the National Guard.
很快会来救我们
should be showing up any day now.
没有军队了
There is no Army.
什么意思
What do you mean?
没有政府 没有医院 没有警察
There's no government, no hospitals, no police.
全没了
It's all gone.
真的吗
For real?
真的
Serious.
那我妈妈呢
What about my moms?
我的孩子 还有我老婆呢
My kids? And my old lady?
你有没有爪机什么的
Yo, you got a cell phone.
让我们给家里打个电话
or somomething that we can call our families?
你还不明白吗
You just don't get it, do you?
电话没用 电脑没用
No phones, no computers.
就我们所知
As far as we can see,
至少一半人都死了
at least half of the population has been wiped out.
有可能更多
Probably more.
- 不可能 - 你自己看看去
- Ain't no way. - See for yourself.
阳光感觉真好
Damn, the sun feels good.
天啊 他们都死了
Good lord. They're all dead.
从没想过再见到这些铁丝网我会这么高兴
Never thought I'd be so happy to see these fences.
你还没告诉我们
You never said…
你们是怎么进来的
how the hell did you get in here in the first place?
在那个警卫塔旁边的铁丝网上开了个洞
Cut a hole in that fence over there by that guard tower.
有那么轻松吗
That easy, huh?
有志者事竟成
Where there's a will there's a way.
你说起来倒容易
Easy for you to say.
这到底怎么回事 传染病吗
So what is this, like a disease?
对 而且我们都被感染了
Yeah, and we're all infected.
被感染了是什么意思
What do you mean infected?
像艾滋病之类的吗
Like aids or something?
如果我杀死你 冲着你胸脯来一箭
If I was to kill you, shoot an arrow in your chest,
你就会变成这种东西
you'd come back as one of these things.
我们所有人都会这样
It's gonna happen to all of us.
这群三脚猫不可能
Ain't no way that these Robbin Hood cats are.
干掉这么多怪物
responsible for killing all these freaks.
外面至少有50具尸体
Must be 50 bodies out here.
你从哪来
Where'd you come from?
亚特兰大
Atlanta.
要去哪里
Where are you headed?
目前来看 哪也不去
For now, nowhere.
你们可以在水源那边住下
I guess you can take that area down there near the water.
应该挺舒服的
Should be comfortable.
我们要用那片地来种庄稼
We're using that field for crops.
我们会帮你把东西搬出来
We'll help you move your gear out.
不用了
That won't be necessary.
我们消灭了这些行尸 这座监狱属于我们
We took out these walkers. This prison is ours.
等会 小子
Slow down, cowboy.
你弄坏了我们门上的锁
You snatched the locks off our doors.
如果你想的话 我们可以给你新锁
We'll give you new locks, if that's how you want it.
这是我们的监狱 我们先到这的
This is our prison. We were here first.
你们是被锁在杂物间里吧
Locked in a broom closet?
我们攻下这里 还你们自由
We took it, set you free.
这里属于我们 我们撒下了鲜血
It's ours. We spilled blood.
我们要搬回我们的牢房区
We're moving back into our cell block.
你们只能重找一个
You'll have to get your own.
那本就是我的牢房区 里面还有我的东西
It is mine. I've still got personal artifacts in there.
横竖都归我
That's about as mine as it gets.
我们可以想个两全其美的办法
Maybe let's try to make this work out so everybody wins.
- 我觉得没可能 - 我也是
- I don't see that happening. - Neither do I.
我死也不回那个食堂
I ain't going back in that cafeteria for one more minute.
还有其他牢房区
There are other cell blocks.
你也可以离开
You could leave.
去外面碰碰运气
Try your luck out on the road.
如果这三个娘娘腔能干掉这么多怪物
If these three pussies can do all this,
那我们也能清理出一个牢房区
the least we can do is take out another cell block.
用什么清理
With what?
这位老兄会给我们一些真正的武器
Atlanta here will spot us some real weapons.
对吗 「老大」
Won't you, boss?
食堂的食物储备有多少
How stocked is that cafeteria?
肯定有很多
It must have plenty of food.
让你们五个维持了近一年
Five guys lasting almost a year?
你们几个看着都没饿过
It sure as hell don't look like anybody's been starving.
- 只剩一点了 - 我们要一半
- There's only a little left. - We'll take half.
作为交换 我们帮你们清理出一个牢房区
In exchange, we'll help clear out a cell block.
你没听见吗 只剩一点了
Didn't you hear him? There's only a little left.
除了交换食物你们有别的选择吗
Bet you got more food than you got choices.
交出食物 我们才帮你
You pay, we'll play.
我们帮你清理 然后那区牢房归你
We'll clear out a block for you then you keep to it.
好吧
All right.
但我们先说清楚
But let's be clear…
如果我看见你动我的人一根毫毛
if we see you out here anywhere near our people,
哪怕只闻到一点点你的气息
if I so much as even catch a whiff of your scent,
我会杀了你
I will kill you.
成交
Deal.
这样能止住血吧
It has to stop eventually, right?
已经不怎么流血了
It slowed down quite a bit already.
如果我们能帮他挺过这关
If we can get him through this…
我们可以的
We can get him through this.
我们需要准备拐杖了
We'll need crutches.
我们现在需要抗生素
Right now we could use some antibiotics.
止疼药 还有消毒纱布
and painkillers, some sterile gauze.
这里应该有医务室
There's got to be an infirmary here.
如果有的话 我们会找到的
If there is, we'll find it.
这下生孩子就更不利了
It's got to be worse about delivering the baby.
看着我 我看起来担心吗
Look at me. Do I look worried?
你看起来又脏又恶心
You look disgusting.
你也是
So do you.
我们会挺过去的
We'll get through this.
食物储藏室在后面
Pantry's back here.
你们没试过从这里逃出去吗
You never tried to break out of here?
我们想把门卸掉
Yeah, we tried to take the doors off.
但是只要往外瞧一眼
But if you make one peep in here,
那些怪物就会堆在门外
then those freaks'll be lined up outside the door growling,
嘶吼着想要进来
trying to get in.
窗户栏杆太坚固 黑巨人都掰不开
Windows got bars on there that He-Man couldn't get through.
- 彪形大汉也没用 - 我没啥抱怨的
- Bigger than a 5x8. - You won't find me complaining.
坐了15年牢 睡觉左腿都得搭在外边
Doing 15. My left leg can barely fit on one of those bunks.
他们叫他大块头就是这个原因
Yeah, they don't call him Big Tiny for nothing.
你们扯够了吗
You done jerking each other off?
我都等半天了
Sick of waiting back here.
这就是你说的「一点食物」
This what you call a little bit of food?
不经吃
Goes fast.
可以分你一袋玉米 一些金枪鱼
You can have a bag of corn, some tuna fish…
我们说的是一半 商量好的
We said half. That's the deal.
- 里面是什么 - 别打开
- What's in there? - Don't open that.
他自找的
He wanted to know.
好想用我自己的尿壶撒尿
Can't wait for my own pot to piss in.
让他和我们一块去真是蠢死了
It was stupid of us to let him go.
清空整间牢房 我们五个人就够了
We cleared this whole cell block, just the five of us.
这事可能会发生在每个人身上
It could have happened to anyone.
没了他我们怎么办
What are we gonna do without him?
别乱想
Hey, stop it.
好吗 别想了
All right? Stop it.
他还在
He's still here.
如果他醒过来了
What if he does wake up?
然后呢 他也不能走路了
Then what? He can't even walk.
而我们总是在逃跑
All we do is run.
这个伤不会击垮他的
This won't break him.
好吗
Okay?
他还有你和贝丝
He's got you and Beth.
难道我是唯一敢面对现实的人吗
Am I the only person living in reality here?
那么多困难我们都挺过来了
We've been through so much already.
你也觉得他不行了
You're expecting it, too.
我没有 好吗
I'm not expecting, all right?
我只是以防万一
I am just preparing.
不如你去看看贝丝怎样
Why don't you go check on Beth?
去吧 我会守着他的
Go on. I'll watch him.
你在干什么
What you doing?
我觉得他的裤子
I think he had a hard time walking around.
一边拖地 会很难走
with one side of his pants dragging on the ground.
他可能会被绊倒之类的
You know, he could trip or something.
很有可能他醒不过来了
There's a good chance that he won't wake up.
- 你怎么能如此轻言放弃 - 我没放弃
- Why are you so eager to give up on him? - I'm not giving up on him.
你的语气听起来就是
It sure sounds like it.
我不想让你抱有太大希望
I don't want you to get your hopes too high.
我们没有设备处理类似的情况
We're not equipped to deal with something like this.
- 我们有卡萝尔 - 她不是医生
- We have Carol. - She's not a doctor.
爸爸只教过她怎么照顾婴儿
Dad taught her a few things to help with the baby.
可她止住血了
She stopped the bleeding.
这样就好了
These'll do just fine.
- 吃的来了 - 都有什么
- Food's here. - What you got?
罐装牛肉 罐装玉米 全都是罐头
Canned beef, canned corn, canned cans.
那里还有很多食物
There's a lot more where this came from.
情况有好转吗
Any change?
血止住了 没有发烧
Bleeding is under control and no fever,
但呼吸很吃力 脉搏也非常低
but his breath is labored and his pulse is way down.
他还没睁过眼
and he hasn't opened his eyes yet.
拿出我的手铐 给他戴上
Take my cuffs, put them on him.
我不会冒一点风险的
I'm not taking any chances.
那些囚犯怎么办
So what about those prisoners?
我们会帮他们
We're gonna help them.
清扫他们自己的单元区
clear out their own cell block,
然后他们住那边 我们在这边
and then they'll be there and we'll be here.
- 同一屋檐下 - 我不会放弃这个监狱
- Living beside each other. - I'm not giving up this prison.
他们有枪吗
Do they have guns?
我只看见一把
I only saw one.
我也不知道这可不可行
Yeah, I don't know if it's gonna work.
你还有别的选择吗
Well, what are your options?
或者杀了他们
Kill them.
如果你觉得那是最佳选择的话
If that's what you think is best.
你现在又说杀人没事…
You s… you say this now…
我知道我不是个好妻子
Look, I know that I'm a shitty wife.
也不是年度荣誉妈妈
and I'm not winning any mother of the year awards,
但是你必须知道
but I need you to know that…
我从来没觉得你心里有一丝歹意
not for one second do I think there is malice in your heart.
你不是冷血杀手 这点我很清楚
You're not a killer, and I know that.
我知道 所以
I know that, so…
为了大家的安全 去做该做的事吧
so do whatever you gotta do to keep this group safe.
此事问心无愧
And do it with a clear conscience.
能用枪 干嘛还用要这个
Why do I need this when I got this?
除非你被逼到绝路
You don't fire guns,
否则不能开枪
not unless your back's up against a wall.
它们循着声响来
Noise attracts them.
这会惊动它们的
It really riles them up.
我们两两一组 达里尔和T仔走前
We'll go in two by two. Daryl will run point with T.
我和你善后
I'll bring up the rear with you.
不管行尸离你多近
Stay tight, hold formation.
都要守住位置 维持队形
close I'll bring up the walkers get…
一人破坏队形 大家都有危险
Anyone breaks ranks, we could all go down.
有谁离队
Anyone runs off,
就可能被误认为行尸
they could get mistaken for a walker,
死于头上利斧
end up with an axe to the head.
你需要的就是对准头部
And that's where you aim.
这些行尸只有头部受伤才会真正死去
These things only go down with a head shot.
用不着你告诉我们怎么杀人
You ain't gotta tell us how to take out a man.
它们不是人 他们是别的东西
They ain't men. They're something else.
记住了 瞄准脑袋
Just remember to go for the brain.
发生了什么
What's going on?
- 我们不得不这样 - 只是以防万一
- We had to. - It's just a precaution.
能让我和他独处几分钟吗
You think maybe I could have a minute alone here?
你需要我陪…
Yeah, you want me to…?
不用 就我一个人
No, just by myself.
当然可以
Of course.
我就在外面
I'll be right outside.
爸爸
Dad…
你不用再坚持了
you don't have to fight anymore.
你不用担心我和贝丝
If you're worried about me and Beth, don't.
不用担心我们
Don't worry about us.
我们会彼此照顾 我们会当心的
We'll take care of each other. We'll look out.
我 贝丝和格伦都会小心的
Me, Beth, and Glenn will look out.
去吧 爸爸 没关系的
Go ahead, Dad. It's okay.
平静地去吧
Be peaceful.
你不必继续战斗了
You don't have to fight.
想走就走吧 没关系的
If it's time to go, it's okay.
爸爸 我只想谢谢你
Daddy, I just want to thank you.
所有的一切都谢谢你
For everything, thank you.
这里太暗了
Man, it's too damn dark in here.
武器在面前举高
Gotta hold it up high out in front of you.
你看到它们之前能听到声音
You're gonna hear them before you see them.
它们来了
It's coming!
我以为你在整理食物
I thought you were organizing the food.
比那更好
Even better.
看看这些
Check it out.
你从哪里找到的
Where did you get this?
从医务室
From the infirmary.
剩的不多 但我都拿来了
Wasn't much left, but I cleared it out.
- 你自己去的吗 - 是的
- You went by yourself? - Yeah.
你疯了吗
Are you crazy?
没什么大不了 我杀了两个行尸
No big deal. I killed two walkers.
你 看到这个了吗
You… all right, do you see this?
这发生在全员都在的情况下
This was with the whole group.
我们需要医用供给 我就去找了
We needed supplies, so I got them.
- 我很感谢 但 - 那就别烦老子
- I appreciate that, but… - Then get off my back.
- 卡尔 - 她是你妈妈
- Carl! - She's your mother.
别那样跟她说话
You can't talk to her like that.
听着 你想帮忙很好
Listen, I think it's great that you wanna help…
得冲着脑袋
It's gotta be the brain.
不是肚子 不是心脏 脑袋
Not the stomach, not the heart… the brain.
我听见了 脑袋
I hear you. The brain.
- 像这样吗 - 没错
- Like that? - Hum-uh.
保持队形 这可不是监狱群殴
Stay in tight formation. No more prison riot crap.
缝几针能防止感染
The stitches will help prevent infection.
很不错
It's good.
多亏他教了你这些
It's good that he taught you all this stuff.
他没教我全部
He didn't teach me everything.
我需要你帮我个忙
I need your help with something.
- 现在吗 - 现在
- Now? - Yeah, now.
什么事
What is it?
出去说
Not here.
我不能离开赫谢尔
I can't leave Hershel.
- 这很重要 - 卡萝尔 我不能
- This is important. - Carol, I can't…
- 去吧 有我们 - 不行
- Go on. We got it. - No way.
我们没事的
We'll be fine.
我们很快就回来
We're not gonna be gone long.
- 瑞克说我得… - 我们没事
- Rick said for me… - We're fine.
那好吧
Alright.
我说了 什么感觉都没有 只是抓伤
I'm telling you, I don't feel anything. It's just a scratch.
- 对不起伙计 - 我可以继续战斗
- I'm sorry, man. - I can keep fighting!
你不是把那老头腿砍了救命吗
You cut that old guy's leg off to save his life.
- 你们看咬伤在哪 - 伙计们我没事
- Look at where the bite is. - Guys, I'm fine!
我很好
Just… I'm fine.
看看我 我不会变成行尸的
Look at me… I'm not changing into one of those things.
听着伙计 我们肯定能做些什么
Look, man, there has to be something we can do.
- 我们可以把他关起来 - 隔离他
- Maybe we can just lock him up. - Quarantine him.
我们必须做点什么 你们怎么都傻站着
We gotta do something. Why you just standing there?
- 我们必须救他 - 我们没什么能做的
- We gotta save him. - There's nothing we can do.
狗杂种
You son of a bitch.
我没事…
I'm all ri…
你的想法是正常的
Everything you're saying is completely sane.
用行尸做练习没什么不对
You're wanting to use a walker for practice is a sane thing.
我是认真的
I mean it, okay.
我只是需要点时间接受
I'm just… I'm just trying to wrap my mind around it.
洛莉已经晚产了
Lori's overdue.
她剖腹产下卡尔
She had Carl by C-section.
这个孩子很可能也要剖腹产
She's probably gonna have to have this one the same way.
赫谢尔有些经验
Hershel had a little bit of exprience.
但他现在肯定没法做了
but he's not gonna be able to do it anymore.
我需要经验
I need experience.
刚好又有很多死尸
and we have plenty of cadavers.
好的 如我所说 这没什么不对
All right, well, like I said, it's completely sane.
我需要学习如何在不伤害婴儿的情况下
I need to learn how to cut through the abdomen and the uterus.
切开腹部和子宫
without cutting the baby.
为何不呢
Why not?
我来吧
I'll do it.
好的
Okay.
跟我来 来啊
Hey, follow me. Come on.
这边 过来
Right here, come on.
跟我来 这就对了
Follow me. That's right.
来吧 快啊
There we go. Come on!
你看到他神情了吗
You see the look on his face?
如果他敢图谋不轨
He makes one move.
你吭一声我就干掉他
Just give me a signal.
- 我才不开门 - 你必须开
- I ain't open to that. - Yes, you are.
如果你想要这个牢房区
If you want this cell block,
就得开门
you're gonna open that door.
只开一扇 别开两扇
Just the one, not both of them.
因为我们要控制住形势
Because we need to control this.
准备好了吗
You bitches ready?
别担心
I got this.
- 我说了只开一扇 - 世事无常嘛
- I said one door! - Shit happens.
T仔 补位
T, mind the gap.
它朝我扑来 老兄
It was coming at me, bro.
是的 我懂
Yeah, yeah, I get it.
我懂
I get it.
世事无常
Shit happens.
不
No!
别动
Easy now.
我追他
I got him.
跪下
Man, get down on your knees.
我们跟刚才的事毫无关系
We don't have no affiliation to what just happened.
快告诉他 奥斯卡
Tell him, Oscar.
别说了 老兄
Stop talking, man.
让我进去 让我进去
Let me back in, man. Let me back in!
开门啊老兄 开门
Open it up, man! Open up!
你最好跑
You'd better run.
怎么了
What's happening?
做点什么啊
Do something!
来人啊 救命啊
Somebody help! Somebody!
救命啊
Please help!
快啊
Come on.
不
No!
那事与我们无关
We ain't had nothing to do with that.
你不知道吗 你肯定知道
You didn't know? You knew.
达里尔 现在就一了百了
Daryl, let's end this now.
先生 求你了 一定要听我说
Sir, sir, you gotta listen to me, please!
是阿克塞尔的主意 他是坏人 与我们无关
It was Axel, he was bad. It was't us.
- 你们想得倒美 - 你看到他对大块头做了什么
- Oh, that's convenient. - You saw what he did to Tiny.
他是我死党
He was my friend.
求你了 我们和他不同
Please, we ain't like that.
我喜欢摆弄药品 但我不会杀人
I like my pharmaceuticals, but I'm no killer.
奥斯卡是修理工
Oscar here is a beater.
他也不会杀人
and he ain't very good at it neither.
我们不是嗜血杀手 他们才是
We ain't the violent kind, they were!
求你了 我发誓是真的 我不想死
Please, I swear to God! I wanna live!
你呢
What about you?
我过去从未求人饶命
I ain't never pleaded for my life.
现在也不会
And I ain't about to start now.
要杀要刮随你
So you do what you gotta do.
天呐
Oh, man.
我认识这些人
I knew these guys.
他们都是好人
These were good men.
我们走
Let's go.
你就把我们丢在这里吗
So you're just gonna Let'sleave us in here?
这太残酷了
Man, this is sick.
我们会封锁这片牢房
We're locking down this cell block.
从现在开始 监狱的这部分属于你们
From now on, this part of the prison is yours.
爱要不要 这是当初的约定
Take it or leave it. That was the deal.
你以为这残酷
You think this is cruel?
外面的世界更残酷
You don't wanna know what's outside.
你们已经很幸运了
Consider yourselves the lucky ones.
你朋友的事我很遗憾
Sorry about your friends, man.
给个小建议
A word of advice…
把尸体抬出去 烧掉
take those bodies outside and burn them.
赫谢尔刚没呼吸了
Hershel stopped breathing.
妈妈救了他
Mom saved him.
是真的
It's true.
没发烧
Still no fever.
爸爸
Daddy?
Daddy.
爸爸
过来
Come here.
我们明天开始清理
We'll start cleaning momorrow.
好的 这样卡尔就能
Yeah, we'll give Carl a safe place to.
安全的生活了
do whatever he does these days.
你要知道 我从不认为你是个坏母亲
For the record, I… I don't think you're a bad mother.
但是个坏妻子
Well, wife is a different story.
正如誓言所说 「不论好坏」
For better or worse, right?
我们该怎么办 雇律师
I mean, what are we gonna do… hire lawyers.
然后离婚 分财产吗
and get divorced and split our assets?
我们找到了食物 救了赫谢尔的命
We got food. Hershel's alive.
今天是个好日子
Today was a good day.
如果不是你 他就死了
He'd be dead if it weren't for you.
你是最先反应过来的
You're the one that acted fast.
如果你没有对他截肢…
If you hadn't done what you did, then…
我还以为你是来聊我们的事
I thought maybe you were coming out here to talk about us.
也许我们间已没什么好说了
Maybe there's nothing to talk about anymore.
我们很感激你所做的一切
We're awful grateful for what you did.